<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<conversations>
	<!--
		This script adds a new dialogue option to Wardens Esther in the Stilt that adds a bit of extra dialogue referencing Tealeaves and who they are.
	-->
	<conversation ID="WardenEsthers" Load="Merge">
		<start ID="Welcome" Load="Merge">
			<choice GotoID="Ava_Tealeaves_Tealeaves" IfNotTestState="Ava_Tealeaves_TealeavesDied">
				<text>What can you tell me about the plant near Tszappur's tent?</text>
			</choice>
		</start>
		<node ID="Ava_Tealeaves_Tealeaves" Inherits="Welcome">
			<text>Oh, that's Tealeaves. They've only arrived recently and they're still discovering themselves, but they're of a mind to remain here for the time being as a chandler. If you need a recoiler, they would be the one to ask.</text>
			<choice GotoID="Ava_Tealeaves_Sponsor" IfTestState="Ava_Tealeaves_AskedAboutSponsorship">They mentioned that the Consortium is "spawn-sirring" them?</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="Ava_Tealeaves_Sponsor">
			<text>{{emote|*The wardens laugh.*}}
			
			They mean to say that they're being sponsored. They've an agreement with the Consortium; they are provided with goods to sell, and in exchange they pay a tithe of their water.</text>
			<choice GotoID="Ava_Tealeaves_Worrying">That's worrying.</choice>
			<choice GotoID="Welcome">I had other questions.</choice>
			<choice GotoID="End">Live and drink.</choice>
		</node>
		<node ID="Ava_Tealeaves_Worrying" Inherits="Ava_Tealeaves_Sponsor">
			<text>I thought so too. Given the nature of the request, I made sure that I was present during the negotiations, and the church retains full authority to make changes to the sponsorship's terms as needed. The Consortium lacks a permanent fixture within the Stiltgrounds, and so thus far they have been willing to acquiesce if it means having a representative within the bazaar.
			
			Don't worry. We intend to ensure that they retain their independence and have space to grow without the Consortium making them into a tool to be used. I hope that helps to soothe your fears.</text>
		</node>
	</conversation>
</conversations>
